

### PROFILE INFO -

#### Web Designer

Highly self-motivated and goal-oriented Web Designing Engineer with 6 years of experience as Assistant Professor looking for a full-time opportunity that flexes my skills. Re-entering the workforce after taking four years off to raise a children while staying engaged with the industry through occasional freelance work.

# **SWATI ANANTWAR**

QA ENGINEER / ASST. PROFESSOR



# PERSONAL SKILLS

- Padagogy
- · Problem Solving
- Mentorship
- Time Management
- Team Player
- Positive Attitude
- Written and Verbal communication

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Python
- Selenium
- · Web Designing
- JAVA/C++
- HTML5/CSS
- Oracle/MySql

### **PROJECTS**

- Data Integrity And Security In Cloud - Linux and JAVA
- Weather crop Management -.Net , MySql
- Student Information System -.Net, Mysql
- Weather temperature recording

- C++

# **WORK EXPERIENCE** –

2009 - 2016

# ASSISTANT PROFESSOR, HVPM ENGINEERING INSTITUTE, AMRAVATI, INDIA

- Instrumental in department planning and operations as well as development and implementation of university policies and laws
- Initiated, facilitated, and moderated computer science-related course discussions in accordance with curriculum
- Planned, designed, and revised syllabi, curriculum, instruction content, and other materials as required
- Provided student body with counsel and direct supervision in laboratory work and issues with coursework
- Stayed abreast of advancements in computing, technology, programming, and syntax

2016 - 2020

### **UNITED STATES**

- Full Time Parent
- Roller Skating Coach in New Jersey.
- Personal Tutor for "SANKSKRIT" [ Ancient Indian Language ].
- "Event Manager", I was helping my friend in arranging events in New Jersey.

2020 - 2023

### **LUXEMBOURG**

- Family Project
- Reconversion

### **EXTRA ACTIVITIES**

- Mentor Of 120 Girls in HVPM COET Hostel (Hostel In charge) and member of AntiRagging committee.
- Youth Festival Manager of H.V.P.M.C.O.E.T of Amravati University in 2012
- Active member Of "ANKUR" Social Service Institute.
- Awarded with 'BEST PERSNALITY OF THE COLLEGE -2008' and GIRLS
  REPRESENTATIVE of IT section(2007-08)
- Active member of "NSS" (NATIONAL SOCIAL SERVICE).
- University Badminton Player (Amt University) From 2004-2010.

### **HOBBIES**

- Painting
- Badminton/Roller skating
- Cooking

### EDUCATION —

MAY 2016	$\mathcal{A}$	IN IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT
		Welingker Institure of
		Management, Mumbai
JUL 2014 JUL 2016	$\Diamond$	MASTER'S OF ENGINEERING IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGG
		S.G.B.A. University, Maharastra,
		India
JUL 2004		BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INFORMATION
<b>JUL 2008</b>		TECHNOLOGY
		S.G.B.A. University, Maharastra,
		India

DOCT CDADUATE DIDI OMA IN MANACEMENT

# **PUBLISHED PAPERS** -

Paper published in International Journal / National Conference

- "Data Integrity And Security In Cloud" in International Journal IJARCET, in Volume 1, Issue7, on 7 Sept 2012.(ISSN -2278-1323)
- "Cloud Computing and Security Models: A Survey" in IJESIT of volume 1, Issue 2, in Nov 2012 (ISSN-2319-5967)
- "Simplified Approach of Artificial Neural Network: Strengths And Weaknesses" in IJEIT of volume 1, Issue 4, (ISSN-2277-3754)
- "Methodology For Data Mining" in IJCSCSE. of volume 2, Issue 4, (ISSN-2277-9477)
- Presented project in International Conference on "BALL TRACKING" during 15th to 17th Jan 2013
- Paper presented on "Analysis And Innovations in Content Based or multimedia Search Engine" in National Conference on Information And Communication Tech.
- Secured 1st position in E-Vidya National Level Technical paper presentation Event in 2007